T/L Leung Ho Yin Tiga

- +852 6236-1782
- tiga.leunghoyin@gmail.com
- LinkedIn:

 www.linkedin.com/in/tiga-ho-
- Skype : iam.tiga

yin-leung

ABOUT ME

I am a research assistant at The Chinese University of Hong Kong, advised by Professor Zhou Bolei in the CUHK Multimedia Lab(MMLAB).

My research interests are in the intersection of robotics and mechatronics, artificial intelligence and control system. Currently, I am focusing on the indoor navigation problem, utilizing a hybrid approach of model-based and learning-based approach.

Prior to my research experience at CUHK, I was working in SenseTime as a Researcher Intern.

I was one of the members in the Autonomous Driving Research Group. Participated research and development work related to path planning and control.

Besides, I designed and developed a 1/10 scale fully autonomous car that mimic the autonomous driving system pipeline.

SKILLS

Able to speak and write English and Chinese fluently.

Well Experienced with Robotics Operating System(ROS), Linux Development Environment, MATLAB, AutoDesk Inventor, TensorFlow, Arduino, Nvidia TX1/2 development, STM32.
4+ years coding experience with Python and C++.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Engineering Major in Mechanical and Automation Minor in Computer Science The Chinese University Hong Kong 2013-2018

Area of study mainly focus on Robotics and Mechatronics.

Enrolled relevant coursework:
Advanced Robotics, Mechatronics System,
Embedded System, Control System, Fundamental
of Artificial Intelligence, Software Engineering.

EXPERIENCE

Research Assistant

The Chinese University of Hong Kong | Hong Kong | September. 2019 - Now

Conducting research related to Indoor Navigation. Designing and Building up the robots for experiments.

- Built up a mobile robot with ROS and PyRobot Library supported.
- Conducting experiments with Al-habitat.
- Researching a hybrid framework that combines learning-based navigation techniques with model-based planning and control method.

Researcher Intern

SenseTime Group Limited | Hong Kong | June.2018 – August.2019

Conducting research on Path Planning Algorithm of an Autonomous Driving Car. Participating the R&D process of a 1/10 scale autonomous driving car.

- Developed a 1/10 scale autonomous driving car that mimic the level4 autonomous driving system pipeline as a commercialized educational product for different high school in Hong Kong and Mainland China.
- Participated in the research work on RRT-Star Path Planning Algorithm
- Researched and Implemented different SLAM Algorithm.
- Developed a simulation environment for car-like robot using Gazebo.